Episode 16
第 16 集
Master, Mrs. Mu is coming.
少爷，穆夫人来了。
all.
全部。
Why are you here suddenly?
你怎么突然来了？
Tuan...
团...
What do you want to do to Hua Shen?
你想对华神做什么？
What do you want?
你想要什么？
Please set him free.
请释放他。
What happened on the wedding day...
婚礼当天到底发生了什么……
It has nothing to do with him.
与他无关。
great.
伟大的。
Mrs. Mu, what did Master say?
慕夫人，师父说什么了？
Will he punish the painter's son?
他会 惩罚画家的儿子吗？
Will you allow me...
你能允许我...
Mr. Fahrenheit's son escaped punishment?
飞轮海先生的儿子 逃脱了惩罚？
How can this happen?
怎么会发生这种事呢？
That person made you angry!
那个人 让你生气了！
Don't you know what happened that day?
你不知道那天发生了什么吗？
You convinced yourself...
你说服了自己...
Something happened that didn't even happen?
发生了一些根本没有发生的事情吗？
This money is enough...
这钱够了...
Enjoy your whole life.
享受你的一生。
Remember, you have to bait him...
记住，你必须引诱他......
To the area I'm talking about.
到我正在谈论的地区。
don't worry.
不用担心。
Remember, don't show your face...
记住，不要露出你的脸...
D Hwangcheong Ragi...
D 黄清拉吉...
And be careful not to be seen...
还有要小心不要被人看到...
By outsiders in this house.
被这屋子里的外人。
Otherwise you will lose your money...
不然 你会损失你的钱...
And your reputation.
还有你的声誉。
Don't worry, lady. is it so...
别担心，女士。 是这样吗...
I want to go back to the village...
我想回村子...
So I will never come to Hwangcheong again .
所以我再也不会来黄清了 。
It's hard to trap him.
想要困住他很难。
Do you want to give up now?
现在你想放弃吗？
of.
的。
Isn't it a waste of time?
这不是浪费时间吗？
I don't want a painter's son..
我不想要画家的儿子..
Will I be punished?
我会受到惩罚吗？
I think why...
我想为什么...
You hate Fahrenheit's son more...
你更讨厌飞轮海的儿子……
From me?
从我？
The man is known for his disorderly behavior.
该男子因其行为不检点而闻名。
That person did a lot of bad things...
那个人做了很多坏事...
But Maid Hua protected him...
但花姑娘却保护了他……
Rather than being punished.
而不是受到惩罚。
That too...
那个也是...
I have dirty thoughts about you.
我对你有肮脏的想法。
Of course I really hate that person.
当然， 我真的很讨厌那个人。
Mr. favoritism.
先生偏袒。
He always protects his wife.
他永远保护他的妻子。
Even though my relatives committed crimes ...
尽管我的亲戚犯了罪 ...
He hesitated to punish them.
他 犹豫着要不要惩罚他们。
He doesn't care if you're dissatisfied.
他不在乎你是否不满意。
Do evil and repay evil.
行恶必报恶。
It's not a waste of time.
这不是浪费时间。
Is this true, mistress?
这是真的吗，小姐？
What benefit can you get from it?
您如何从中受益？
At least I know...
至少我知道...
I have loyal people by my side.
我身边有忠诚的人。
If you follow the timeline of your past life ...
如果你遵循前世的时间线 ...
Now is the time...
现在是时候了...
Anak Angkat Broker...
Anak Angkat 经纪人...
The person who ran away has appeared.
逃跑的人出现了。
Lady, don't kill me!
小姐，别杀我！
Don't kill me!
别杀我！
Broker Chen...
经纪人陈...
I don't think anyone will recognize you...
我想没有人 会认出你...
What if you change your name to Su Ying?
如果你把名字改成苏樱怎么办？
If it's really cruel...
如果真的很残忍的话...
I can't find you.
我找不到你。
Even though I committed many crimes ...
虽然我犯了很多罪 ...
You still want to live happily with your family.
你还是想和家人幸福快乐地生活。
You are too greedy.
你太贪心了。
Miss...
错过...
I am Mu Yunping's son...
我是穆云平的儿子……
A person falsely accused of embezzlement..
一个人被诬告贪污..
1 year ago.
1年以前。
I think you remember.
我想你还记得。
Now I want to take revenge on you.
现在我想向你报仇。
Do you feel you are being treated unfairly?
您是否觉得自己受到了不公平的对待？
There is no hatred without cause.
没有无缘无故的仇恨。
If you want my life...
如果你想要我的命...
take it
拿去
But I...
但是我...
So you free my children and grandchildren.
所以你 释放了我的孩子和孙子。
They are innocent.
他们是无辜的。
How dare you say “not guilty”?
你怎么敢说“无罪”？
Please, ma'am. Don't kill them!
请，女士。 别杀他们！
Just send it to me.
只需将其发送给我即可。
I can free your family...
我可以释放你的家人...
But I want you to go back to the imperial city ...
但我要你回皇城 ……
It also provides information...
它还提供信息...
Assistant Hua abused his colleagues...
华助理 辱骂同事……
And makes him die.
并且让他死。
Are you so loyal to Hua Assistant?
你对华助理就这么忠诚吗？
No, it doesn't.
不，事实并非如此。
Now all I can say is that Hua Assistant is very powerful.
现在我只能说，华助理很强大。
If I testify against him...
如果我 作证反对他...
I'm worried that my child will be like that...
我担心我的孩子会变成这样...
If Aide Hwa can be indicted...
如果爱德华可以被起诉...
You do not have to worry...
你不必担心...
Family safety, right?
家庭安全吧？
great.
伟大的。
There is one condition. i want you...
有一个条件。 我要你...
Please let my daughter go...
请放过我的女儿...
And her newborn child first.
首先是她刚出生的孩子。
Do you know where Huiyang District is?
你知道惠阳区在哪里吗？
This area covers thousands of miles...
这片区域，绵延数千里……
Leg Hwangcheong.
黄清腿。
Why are you suddenly asking this?
你怎么突然问这个？
Fortunately, this part has not changed.
幸运的是，这部分没有改变。
what?
什么？
Hua Rongzhou, 마숙.
Hua Rongzhou, 마숙.
ma'am.
女士。
Follow me.
跟我来。
number of animals.
动物的数量。
Time is running out.
时间不多了。
I wish you could find someone...
我希望你能找到一个人...
In a border town.
在一个边境小镇。
where? WHO?
在哪里？ WHO？
The small town was called Huiyang District.
这个小镇 被称为惠阳区。
The person I want to find...
我想找的人...
Go and investigate...
去调查一下吧...
If you are pregnant...
如果您怀孕了...
Someone who just moved there and lives alone.
一个刚搬到那里 并且独自居住的人。
What is her name?
她叫什么名字？
I don't remember.
我不记得了。
In my past life...
在我的前世......
Mu Yao found out about the broker's adopted son...
穆瑶 发现了经纪人养子的事情……
How many times have you moved...
您搬过几次家...
A year since my father passed away...
我父亲去世一年了......
Jonggan Bantuan Jongyeran
Jonggan Bantuan Jonyeran
Mereka tunggu dan Jumpa Broker Qian.
Mereka tunggu dan Jumpa 经纪人钱。
It's been over half a year...
已经半年多了...
After his father was exiled...
他的父亲被流放后......
I think this will be enough.
我认为这就足够了。
Anak Angkat Broker Security...
Anak Angkat 经纪人安全...
Relocated to Hoeyang-gu...
搬迁至会阳区...
And Mu Yao You may not see him yet
还有慕瑶 你可能还看不到他
Let me give you a rough idea.
让我给你一个大概的想法。
She is a poor woman.
她是一个可怜的女人。
I might move to Hyeyang County...
我可能会搬到惠阳郡...
For a month or two.
一两个月。
He lives alone.
他一个人住。
Her husband may have just died.
她的丈夫 可能刚刚去世。
He has no family by his side.
他身边没有家人。
I don't remember either...
我也不记得了...
How long has he been pregnant?
他怀孕多久了？
But I'm sure she hasn't given birth yet.
但我确信她还没有生孩子。
He has an adoptive mother named Su Ying ...
他有一个养母，名叫苏樱 ……
It's a pseudonym.
这是一个化名。
But her adoptive mother may be hiding.
但她的养母 可能躲起来了。
The person I'm looking for is actually...
我要找的人 其实是……
Mom came to pick him up.
妈妈来接他了。
Is it too difficult?
是不是太难了？
This is all the information I know.
这就是我所知道的全部信息。
This is what I got from Mu Yao's statement...
这是我从慕瑶的话中得到的信息……
First in court.
首先出庭。
Jong Ye-ran discovered him..
钟艺兰发现了他..
But I can't ask him for help now.
但我现在不能向他求助。
ma'am.
女士。
I will find this woman.
我会找到这个女人。
Is that true?
真的吗？
You have provided enough information .
你已经提供了足够的信息 。
When you see that person...
当你看到那个人的时候...
From now on, I'll give you whatever you want!
从今往后，你想要什么我都给你！
When I see that person...
当我看到那个人的时候...
Do you want me to bring him back?
你想让我把他带回来吗？
Don't bring him back...
别把他带回来...
Others don't see him.
其他人看不到他。
When you see that person...
当你看到那个人的时候...
Make sure Su Ying is safe.
确保苏樱安全。
If the person doesn't want to plead guilty...
如果这个人不愿意认罪的话...
Threatening her with children...
用孩子来威胁她……
In the womb of an adopted child.
在被收养的孩子的子宫里。
great. I go first.
伟大的。 我先走了。
That's just an empty threat.
那只是空洞的威胁。
Don't hurt your adopted child...
不要伤害你领养的孩子...
and her unborn child.
还有她未出生的孩子。
Don't be too afraid of him.
别太怕他。
If the person is afraid...
如果这个人害怕...
It can influence her content .
它可以影响她的内容 。
great.
伟大的。
Do you know what I just said?
你知道我刚才说什么吗？
Monarch...
君主...
Please let me divorce sir.
先生，请让我离婚。
If Yellen did something wrong...
如果耶伦做错了什么...
You can keep talking
你可以继续说
There is no need to divorce that person.
没有必要和那个人离婚。
I didn't come here suddenly.
我并不是突然来到这里的。
You and I are not destined to be together...
我和你 是注定不会在一起的……
Therefore, we must follow each other's instructions.
因此，我们必须遵循彼此的指示。
nonsense!
废话！
You are married.
你结婚了。
This has nothing to do with fate.
这与命运无关。
Is it because of the concubine?
是因为妾的缘故吗？
It has nothing to do with that person.
和那个人没有任何关系。
This is my opinion.
这是我的意见。
If you take the initiative...
如果你主动...
To give Yelan a government...
给夜兰一个政府……
I thought you wanted to make peace.
我以为你想讲和
How can this be?
怎么会这样？
actually...
实际上...
Actually, I've wanted a divorce for a long time...
其实 我想离婚很久了...
Because I protected you from the arrows.
因为我保护你免受箭矢伤害。
I don't want to...
我不想...
give me a concubine
给我一个妾
I reached that point...
我达到了那个地步...
I don't want to live with that person anymore .
我不想再和那个人住在一起了 。
you are still young
你还很年轻
I understand, you seem nervous.
我明白，你看起来很紧张。
Many of us have been through it.
我们很多人都经历过。
You must learn...
你必须学...
Accept it...
接受...
Don't escape like this.
别就这样逃跑。
Wouldn’t my master allow divorce?
我的主人不允许 离婚吗？
If so, I must ask for your help.
如果是这样， 我必须请求你的帮助。
you!
你！
ma'am.
女士。
Just forget it.
把它忘了吧。
Because you don't want to take my advice...
因为你不想接受我的建议...
I'll give you a month...
我给你一个月...
Calm down and think hard.
冷静下来， 认真思考。
Still, if you insist...
不过，如果你坚持的话...
I will send someone to testify...
我会派人去作证...
your divorce.
你的离婚。
I won't regret it.
我不会后悔的。
ma'am.
女士。
He told me to come to his house and invite him.
他让我去他家邀请他。
He wants to discuss something with you .
他想和你讨论一些事情 。
Please lead the way, Gao Enxi.
请高恩熙带路。
ma'am.
女士。
I think you are still young.
我想你还年轻。
He will understand...
他会明白的...
And accept it someday.
并有一天接受它。
Teacher, don't worry too much...
老师您别太担心...
About how to convince him.
关于如何说服他。
persuade?
说服？
Are my actions to persuade him right?
我劝说他的行为正确吗？
He has freedom of choice...
他有选择的自由……
It's different from me
这和我不一样
iced coffee.
冰咖啡。
It's been a while since you came...
你来已经有一段时间了...
Ketaman species.
科塔曼种。
It's very quiet here.
这里很安静。
Thanks for checking out, Miss Chi.
感谢您的关注，池小姐。
You just came out...
你刚出来...
At his residence?
在他住处？
Yeah, I was there for a while...
是的，我在那里呆了一段时间...
I just want to go.
我只想走。
You are smart.
你很聪明。
Know that it's useless...
知道没有用...
Forgive your husband...
原谅你的丈夫...
So you came here to forgive him.
所以你 来这里是为了原谅他。
Kak Qi and I came at the wrong time.
我和卡克奇 来得不是时候。
You just want to leave.
你只想离开。
sorry to bother you.
很抱歉打扰你。
Sir, there is one thing I would like to ask...
先生，我想请教一件事……
And he's still waiting for his wife.
而他还在等他的妻子。
go away. No one is stopping you.
离开。 没有人阻止你。
If I visit here again...
如果我再次访问这里...
Thank you for coming to meet me.
谢谢你来见我。
Madam, please.
女士，请。
Mr. Qi, I think so...
齐先生，我想是的……
You don't really like Cik Puan Hua, do you ?
你不太喜欢Cik Puan Hua，是吗 ？
Yeah, so?
所以啊？
why?
为什么？
Does there have to be a reason to hate someone?
讨厌一个人一定要有理由吗？
Tuan.
团。
Madam, I am the owner...
小姐，我是主人……
Embroidery workshop shop.
刺绣作坊店。
Please raise your hand.
请举手。
What is this for?
这个是来做什么的？
I want to make clothes for that person.
我想为那个人做衣服。
Because the body type is the same...
因为体型是一样的...
And since you are here too...
既然 你也在这里...
I need measurements.
我需要测量。
Tuan...
团...
Why did you meet your mom?
你为什么遇见你妈妈？
naught.
什么也没有。
If you want to divorce...
如果你想离婚...
It goes faster if you ask me for help.
如果你向我寻求帮助，事情会进展得更快。
no.
不。
Teacher, I'm ready.
老师，我准备好了。
There are many maids in your house .
你家里有很多女佣 。
There must be some people...
一定有一些人...
A person with a body like Mu Yao.
拥有慕瑶这样身材的人。
Why should you use me?
你为什么要使用我？
After all, she is now Zhong Yeran's lover.
毕竟，她 现在是钟野然的爱人了。
Flirting is not good...
调情可不好...
The owner's senior mistress.
主人的高级情妇。
Do you think there is...
你认为有没有...
Are there too many maids around me ?
我身边的女佣是不是太多了 ？
Mu Yao and I have a lot in common...
我和慕瑶有 很多共同点……
So we are together...
于是我们就在一起了...
And get to know each other.
并互相了解。
Even without Jong Ye-ran...
即使没有钟艺兰...
She doesn't want to marry a member of the Zhong family.
她不想嫁给钟家的人。
why?
为什么？
The Jong family...
郑家...
A 100-year-old family of perfume producers.
一个拥有100年历史的香水生产家族。
So everyone has high expectations...
所以大家都 抱有很高的期望...
I'm against your wife.
我反对你的妻子。
Your Majesty enjoys the highest status here.
陛下 在这里享有最高的地位。
If Mu Yao marries you...
如果慕瑶娶了你……
He can only stay in this house.
他只能呆在这个房子里。
In the end, as a married woman...
最后， 作为一个已婚妇女...
Mu Yao is not allowed to marry you .
沐瑶不许娶你 。
at last...
终于...
Mu Yao learns the art of perfume making .
慕瑶学习香水制作技艺 。
From his father.
来自他的父亲。
He wants to explore the wide world...
他想要探索更广阔的世界……
And don't waste your skills...
并且不要浪费你的技能...
To become a big woman who only cares about herself...
成为一个只关心自己的大女人......
home.
家。
You think so?
你这么认为吗？
I guessed Mu Yao's intentions...
我猜到了慕瑶的意图……
Based on my own views.
根据我自己的看法。
If you don't believe me...
如果你不相信我...
Mu Yao asked himself.
慕瑶自问。
If he had said it himself...
如果是他自己说的话……
It's impossible for that person to lie.
那人不可能说谎。
You are good to go.
你已准备好出发。
Why do I know that person?
我为什么认识那个人？
He looks like a new guy.
他看起来像个新人。
You can hardly see him in Zongbak.
在宗巴克你几乎看不到他。
Why do I feel like I've seen that person before?
为什么我感觉这个人似曾相识？
I heard what the servant said earlier .
我刚才听到仆人说的话了。
He told Gao Eunuchs that Young Master Hua...
他告诉 高太监，华公子……
Released from prison.
出狱了。
Mu Yao acted quickly.
慕瑶动作很快。
Let's go back.
我们回去吧。
Sir, I understand...
先生，我明白了……
Mr. Jong Ye-ran gave instructions.
钟艺兰先生作出指示。
They said it was just a misunderstanding...
他们说这只是一场误会……
And your concubine doesn't want to investigate further.
而你的妾也不想再追究下去。
This is why Hua Shen was released.
这就是华神被释放的原因。
Go ahead and try it. Cover yourself.
继续尝试。 掩护自己。
Don't get the flu.
别得流感。
be careful.
当心。
here. Put your hand in.
这里。 把你的手放进去。
Assistant Hua, your wife is coming.
华助理，你老婆来了。
- father. - Kian!
- 父亲。 - 基安！
membrane.
膜。
Qian, your brother has been imprisoned for a long time.
钱，你弟弟已经被关在监狱里很久了。
How about coming to see my sister?
来看看我姐姐怎么样？
Father, I kept my promise.
父亲，我遵守了诺言。
Can you hear what I'm saying now?
你现在能听到我在说什么吗？
Follow your dad to the reading room.
跟着你爸爸去阅览室。
Kian.
基安.
Brother, calm down.
兄弟，冷静点。
I'll come see my brother later.
稍后我会来看我的兄弟。
Stupid boy!
愚蠢的男孩！
I asked His Majesty for permission...
我请求陛下允许...
Jong Ye-ran and I are getting divorced.
我和钟艺兰要离婚了。
Mu Yao conspired with the master.
穆瑶与师父合谋。
He wants to bring down the Hua Family.
他要扳倒华家。
You are useless.
你真没用。
You can't win a man's heart.
你无法赢得男人的心。
Dad, the first thing that comes to mind is...
爸爸，我 第一个想到的是……
“So what I got…
“所以我得到的...
“Because I did a lot of evil things?”
“因为我做了很多恶事？”
What did you say?
你说什么？
Don't even think about blaming Dad...
更别想责怪爸爸了……
Just because you saved me...
只因为你救了我...
Your brother is out of prison!
你弟弟出狱了！
I can't do that...
我不能那样做...
Because I put my brother in prison...
因为我把我弟弟关进了监狱...
But I want to remind my dad...
但我想提醒我爸爸...
The Hua family is in danger now.
华家 现在正处于危险之中。
I 'm sure people know something about my dad.
我确信人们对我父亲有所了解。
In the end, the father is arrested...
最后， 父亲被捕了……
And there is no escape from punishment.
并且无法逃脱惩罚。
really!
真的吗！
Who doesn't know anything?
谁什么都不知道？
Daddy's not afraid of anything! listen!
爸爸什么都不怕！ 听！
As long as my father maintains his position as special assistant...
只要我父亲继续担任特别助理...
No one will act hastily.
没有人 会仓促行动。
From my father's point of view...
从我父亲的角度来看...
Is the father's power limited to oppressing others?
父亲的权力 仅限于压迫他人吗？
I don't know why dad...
不知道为什么爸爸...
I want to become a special assistant..
我想成为一名特别助理..
But I think...
但我觉得...
Dad supervises all special assistants.
爸爸负责监督所有的特别助理。
Dad has to make a nice scent...
爸爸一定要调制出好闻的香味……
And taking advantage of people...
还利用人...
And he makes his father's dream come true.
他让父亲的梦想成真。
But now my dad is doing the opposite.
但现在 我爸爸却反其道而行之。
A father who pursues power and wealth...
一个追求权力和财富的父亲......
And he began oppressing his father's subordinates.
他 开始压迫他父亲的下属。
top...
顶部...
Dad might be able to see far away...
爸爸也许能看到很远的地方……
But at the same time...
但同时……
Dad was blind to things around him.
爸爸对周围的事物视而不见。
I don't know?
我不知道？
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
What don't you see?
你没看到什么？
What happened to my brother?
我弟弟怎么了？
You probably know better than me why that happened .
你可能比我更清楚为什么会发生这种情况。
Dad climbs higher...
爸爸爬得更高……
The more enemies there are...
敌人越多...
There are more hidden dangers that Dad will face ...
爸爸还将面临更多的隐患 ……
And the father will lose even more ...
而父亲将会失去更多……
When surrounded.
被包围时。
This is karma.
这就是业力。
When my brother was in prison...
当我哥哥入狱时...
I can't find anyone to help me.
我找不到人来帮助我。
That proves my point.
这证明了我的观点。
Why do I look like someone else now?
为什么我现在看起来像别人了？
In the past, I would not have thought about this.
放在以前，我是不会想到这个问题的。
When faced with death...
当面对死亡时...
Even the dumbest people...
即使是最愚蠢的人...
You can see it clearly.
你可以清楚地看到它。
I don't want to scare my dad.
我不想吓到我爸爸。
While there's still time...
趁还有时间...
If Dad is willing to resign now...
如果爸爸现在愿意辞职的话...
Hwa family...
华家...
It will be safe.
会很安全的。
The world is wide.
世界很广阔。
Maybe I can change the name...
也许我可以改个名字……
And I live in the village...
而且我住在村里...
And apply our technology to perfume making.
并将我们的技术 应用于香水制作。
For the benefit of the people.
为了人民的利益。
Worth considering, right?
值得考虑，对吧？
Do you want me to resign?
你想让我辞职吗？
As you said...
如你所说...
Master and son Mu are looking for their father's fault.
师父和穆子 正在寻找父亲的过错。
If my dad resigns now...
如果我爸爸现在辞职...
Won't your father become a victim?
你的父亲不会成为受害者吗？
no.
不。
Now they are trying...
现在他们正在尝试...
Improve their relationship.
改善他们的关系。
No action has been taken yet ...
尚未采取任何行动 ...
And they don't know anything about us.
他们对我们一无所知。
So now is the best time for Dad to resign.
所以现在是爸爸辞职的最佳时机。
at last...
终于...
We and Mu Yao are not enemies.
我们和沐瑶不是敌人。
He won't come after us...
他不会来追我们的……
And we urge you:
我们敦促您：
Why should dad trust you?
爸爸为什么要相信你？
Because I am my father's son.
因为我是我父亲的儿子。
When the bird's nest is overturned...
当鸟巢被掀翻的时候……
The eggs do not remain intact.
鸡蛋不会保持完整。
next month...
下个月...
He will help me...
他会帮助我...
Seraikan Jongyeran.
塞莱坎·琼耶兰。
When the time comes...
在时机成熟时...
And if dad decides to resign ...
如果爸爸决定辞职 ...
I will return to Hua Family...
我 要回华家了……
Face everything with your dad .
和你爸爸一起面对一切 。
If you are reluctant to give up power...
如果你不愿意放弃权力...
I will go.
我要走了。
Whether Fahrenheit falls or rises...
无论华氏度 下降还是上升...
It has nothing to do with me.
这与我无关。
Heeyangdaera
熙阳大拉
Is it too difficult?
是不是太难了？
This is all the information I know.
这就是我所知道的全部信息。
This is what I got from Mu Yao's statement...
这是我从慕瑶的话中得到的信息……
First in court.
首先出庭。
I can't ask for help right now.
我现在无法寻求帮助。
If you're tired, rest.
如果你累了，就休息吧。
I am in no hurry to check this ledger.
我并不急于检查这个账本。
as it were...
就好像……
I discovered a new clue in just a few days.
短短几天，我就发现了新的线索。
What is he?
他是什么？
There is no trace of the broker, but...
没有经纪人的踪迹，但是……
Who buys furniture for their family?
谁为家人购买家具？
I found out that he adopted the child.
我得知这个孩子是他领养的。
That person is trying to sell...
那个人是想卖...
Make him your son.
让他成为你的儿子。
Then, she marries her adopted son...
然后， 她嫁给了她的养子……
Secretly with a man.
偷偷地和一个男人在一起。
He seems to love his son very much.
看来他很爱自己的儿子。
Where is my adopted son's husband...
我养子的丈夫在哪里……
stay?
停留？
They lived outside the city...
他们住在城外...
But they moved several times.
但他们 搬家了好几次。
I think I live in a border town now...
我想我现在住在边境小镇......
But I don't know the exact location.
但我不知道具体位置。
Because I have a clue about my husband...
因为我对我丈夫有一点了解……
It's easier to find a broker...
找经纪人比较容易...
Than find that broker.
不如找到那个经纪人。
great...
伟大的...
Please leave this to me.
请把这个交给我。
I have the resources to look into it .
我有资源去调查它 。
OK. thank you
好的。 谢谢
Why are you being so polite to me?
你为什么 对我这么客气？
Should I say thank you...
我该说谢谢吗...
Because we need your help.
因为我们需要你的帮助。
I heard that Hua Qian went to Zhong Park...
听说花千去中央公园了……
I wanted to meet him a few days ago.
几天前我就想见见他。
do you know about this?
你知道这件事吗？
of.
的。
What do you want to do?
你想让我做什么？
I will follow the previous plan...
我会按照之前的计划...
Please wait for this case to change.
请等待这种情况的改变。
He can't make up his mind...
他拿不定主意……
divorce.
离婚。
said?
说？
Who is there?
谁在那儿？
How are you, Mr. Mu?
穆先生，你好吗？
Why do I do that every time I see it?
为什么我每次看到它都会这样做？
Master Wooyoung, you cannot change...
佑荣大师， 你无法改变……
You have a habit of coming uninvited, right?
你有不请自来的习惯，对吗？
I really want to feel that experience...
我真的很想感受一下那种经历...
Prison life in the imperial castle?
皇宫里的监狱生活？
why?
为什么？
naught.
什么也没有。
i miss you...
我想你...
So I came to see you.
所以我来看你了。
You sent someone to be by my side.
你派了一个人来陪在我身边。
Is it because you miss me too?
是因为你也想念我吗？
I know you are smart.
我知道你很聪明。
What exactly do you want?
你到底想要什么？
listen.
听。
I will no longer be used by anyone.
我不会再被任何人利用了。
You still think...
你还认为...
Did I approach this with bad intentions?
我这样做是出于恶意吗？
ask yourself
问你自己
When do I take advantage of you?
我什么时候利用你？
Who knows.
谁知道。
I can't read your mind , can I?
我读不懂你的心思 ，可以吗？
If I...
如果我...
Who caught you under the tree...
谁把你抓到树下了...
Won't you doubt me?
你不会怀疑我吗？
It's all your fault.
都是你的错。
You scared my parrot.
你 吓坏了我的鹦鹉。
If you don't see it...
如果你没有看到它...
Don't expect to come back with me
别指望跟我一起回来
I'll definitely see it!
我一定会看到的！
Tuan...
团...
you call me
你打给我
Birds don't remember favors.
鸟儿不记得恩惠。
He saw a girl and called her “teacher.”
他看到一个女孩 ，称她为“老师”。
- Come down here! - teacher...
- 下来这里！ - 老师...
Come down here!
下来吧！
There's a snake behind you!
你身后有一条蛇！
Get off now!
现在就下车吧！
Do you want to fly? Otherwise I...
你想飞吗？ 不然我...
fly!
飞！
Tuan...
团...
Someone is coming.
有人来了。
Huangcheng made a very firm request ...
皇城提出了非常坚决的要求 ……
Against single women.
反对单身女性。
If people keep looking at that person ...
如果人们一直看着那个人……
People will say
人们会说
Strict requirements for single women ?
对单身女性要求严格 ？
That person may be a woman from a low family, but...
那人或许是一个出身低贱的女人，但是……
So his behavior is a bit difficult to control.
所以他的行为有点难以控制。
We talked for a while...
我们聊了一会儿...
And someone stole my chance.
有人抢走了我的机会。
Tuan.
团。
Are you looking for another parrot?
您在寻找另一只鹦鹉吗？
I found you in the banquet hall...
我在宴会厅找到你了...
but i can't see you
但我看不到你
When people ask you about ...
当人们问你关于 ...
Everyone said they had never seen you before.
每个人 都说他们以前从未见过你。
How much!
多少！
Did you see the parrot here earlier?
你之前看到过这里的鹦鹉吗？
So is that your parrot?
那是你的鹦鹉吗？
I see you
我看见你
I think I scared him by mistake .
我想我不小心 吓到他了。
How can we help you find it?
我们如何帮助您找到它？
thank you
谢谢
So he lied to me about this.
所以他在这件事上对我撒了谎。
I tell the whole truth.
我说出了全部真相。
I'm not talking about you.
我不是在说你。
Because you know how I feel about you ...
因为你知道我对你的感觉 ...
Can you trust me now?
现在你可以相信我了吗？
trust you?
相信你？
I want to take you with me.
我想带你一起去。
How many days has Hua Rongzhou been gone?
华容舟已经走了多少天了？
About half a month.
大约半个月。
Why didn't he come back?
他为什么没有回来？
Cheongok, Tanpa Hwayongju...
清谷、丹波花龙州……
The maids in this area look helpless.
这一带的女仆们 一脸无奈。
ma'am.
女士。
Huarongzhou.
华容洲。
ma'am!
女士！
how? Have you ever met him?
如何？ 你见过他吗？
Let's talk from the inside. No one can see this.
我们从内部谈谈吧。 没有人能看到这一点。
You worked hard.
你辛苦了。
Go and rest.
去休息吧。
Contract
合同
Ditandatangani oleh Qian Ying dan Mu Yunping
Ditandatangani oleh Qian Ying dan Mu Yunping
nurse...
护士...
Now it's up to Dad.
现在就看爸爸了。
Monarch...
君主...
This is a Buddhist scripture that I recently copied.
这是我最近抄写的一部佛经。
Please take a look.
请看一下。
good job.
好工作。
Monarch...
君主...
Relatives of the two young women are here.
两名年轻女子 的亲戚也在这里。
Is my second aunt here?
我二姨在吗？
A few days ago, that person sent someone...
前几天， 那人派人来了……
I wanted to tell you that he might come to see me.
我想告诉你他可能会来看我。
Yes, he is right.
是的，他是对的。
Mischi's father also sent someone...
米斯基的父亲也派人来了……
Bringing goods from the north...
从北方运来的货物...
For the Mid-Autumn Festival...
为了中秋节...
A few more days.
还有几天。
go away.
离开。
Thank you, my lord.
谢谢您，陛下。
You should go and see it too...
你也应该去看看...
What did your father send?
你父亲寄来了什么？
not needed. I 'll send someone to get it.
不需要。我 会派人去取。
Cik Qi, En. Jin yang datang...
Cik Qi, En. Jin yang datang...
Maid Qi told Miss to bring something.
齐丫鬟吩咐小姐带点东西来。
and. what?
和。什么？
Is your name Jinrin?
你叫金凛吗？
Yes, it's full.
是的，已经满了。
me...
我...
Teacher, I want to go there sometime...
老师，我有时间也想去一趟……
what my father sent me
我父亲寄给我的东西
go away.
离开。
Sometimes I envy them.
有时 我很羡慕他们。
At least they have family visiting them...
至少 还有家人来看望他们……
sometimes.
有时。
They are still young.
他们还年轻。
I brought you here from the village...
我把你从村子里带过来...
Ke Hwangcheong.
柯黄清.
Will you blame me in your heart?
你会在心里埋怨我吗？
Sir, that is impossible.
先生，这是不可能的。
The master's invitation...
大师的邀请...
It's a great opportunity for them.
这对他们来说是一个很好的机会。
How much.
多少。
This is Jongho Park. Be careful with your actions.
这是朴钟浩。 小心你的行为。
How much...
多少...
Take this over there. be careful.
把这个拿到那里。 当心。
Tread carefully.
小心行事。
It's a tiring trip.
这是一次很累的旅行。
Thank you for your hard work, Jinrin.
谢谢你的辛勤工作，津凛。
I'm here to deliver something on behalf of Mr. Chi.
我是来代表迟先生传递一些东西的。
wait.
等待。
This is for Miss Qi.
这是给齐小姐的。
It was full of Miss Qi's favorite things .
里面装满了齐小姐最喜欢的东西 。
I didn't think it was Mr. Chi...
没想到是池先生……
So please worry about Miss Qi.
所以请您担心齐小姐。
Shanzhi, please take these to my room.
山芝，请把这些带到我的房间去。
I want Jin Lin to deliver a message to his father.
我想让金霖 给他父亲转个口信。
Are you trying to disobey my orders?
你想违抗我的命令吗？
Abang's nickname...
阿邦的昵称是...
Miss Qi, since you are here...
齐小姐， 既然你来了……
I think it would be better if you don't call me by my nickname.
我想你最好不要用我的昵称来称呼我。
Do you blame me?
你怪我吗？
I don't dare do that.
我不敢这么做。
Do you really want to get away from me?
你真的想离开我吗？
Miss Chi...
池小姐……
And I am a slave.
而我是一个奴隶。
How can I get you away from me?
我怎样 才能让你远离我？
If I mean nothing to you...
如果我对你来说毫无意义的话...
You won't come here...
你不会来这里...
Want to send my stuff?
想寄我的东西吗？
This is not your job.
这不是你的工作。
Abang's nickname...
阿邦的昵称是...
I embroidered this myself.
这是我自己绣的。
don't worry.
不用担心。
He doesn't care about me anymore.
他不再关心我了。
Gradually he would let me go.
渐渐地， 他就会放开我。
My father arranged a marriage for me.
我父亲 为我安排了一桩婚姻。
Lakaman Bonus
拉卡曼奖金
I'm sure I saw him.
我确定我看到他了。
That useless guy...
那个没用的家伙……
While wandering around this area...
当我在这个地区闲逛时...
These few days.
这几天。
to.
到。
Is that useless boy really here?
那个没用的小子真的在这里 吗？
Yes, I think so.
是的，我想是这样。
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
I don't think he came looking for us.
我不认为他是来找我们的。
I sent someone...
我派人...
Let's follow him quietly.
让我们静静地跟随他吧。
Her clothes are different than before.
她的衣服和以前不一样了。
We must make sure...
我们必须确保...
Before making any plans.
在制定任何计划之前。
Unless he comes looking for us.
除非他来找我们。